Address: Delhi

**Phone:** +91 7869849719

**Email:** surbhigulhana3@gmail.com

# SURBHI GULHANA

## **Summary**

Looking for a responsible and challenging position in an innovative development environment, where i can use my expertise for the potential growth of the organization with opportunities to enrich my knowledge, experience and skills while contributing my best. I have 1.5 years of experience in the development field.

# **Skill Highlights**

- C Programming
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- ReactJS

- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- Bootstrap
- MongoDb
- Altas

### **Experience**

Full Stack Developer – 06/2022 to Current

OmkaTech LLP, Noida

- Database Technology (Firebase, MongoDB) HTML & CSS. JavaScript, Bootstrap & JS Frameworks(NodeJS, React).
- Expert in building fully responsive web apps
- Good knowledge AWS (ec2 instance) and Cpanel.

Mern Developer – 02/2022 to 06/2022

Praedico Global Research Pvt. Ltd, Gwalior

Database Technology (PostgreSQL MongoDB) HTML & CSS bootstrap. JavaScript & JS Frameworks(NodeJS, React)

**Frontend Developer** – 03/2021 to 10/2021

Kanishka Information Technology Pvt. Ltd, Gwalior

#### **Education**

- Master In Computer Science (M.Sc) 2020-2022
  Study Of Mathematics And Allied Science , Jiwaji University ,474001
- Bachlor In Computer Scienec (B.sc) 2017-2020
  Govt Krg Pg Autonomous College, Gwalior M.P
- Post Graduation Deploma In Computer Application
  Makhanlal Chaturvedi National University of Journalism and Communication, Bhopal

# **Projects**

#### • Automatic Logo maker web app,

just enter the brand name click generate logo button and the logo is generated automatically you can also edit and customize the logo.

#### Pharma Management System ,

with the help of this dashboard you can manage your medical store inventory staff salary and product selling, billing system

#### • Online Eyelash Buy System

using this we can buy different king of lashes also with multiple attributes like color, size, length etc

#### • Company Website (Fully Responsive)

In which we have to use multiple react packages.

#### • Virtual Office System

which have three modules admin, team lead, and employee. We can handle tasks, meeting, customer information ,product buy etc.

#### • Covid Awareness Website

Also done many app backend (Admin Panel)

# Language

- English
- Hindi